10bet.com 2006-06-15

# ::: 10BET - The Best You Can Bet ::: - Bet Info

| 

| **  ODDS MENU:**  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---  
  
**Privacy Policy**  
---  

We will process any personal information provided to us or held by us relating to you in the manner set out in this statement. By submitting your information to us and using our web site you confirm your consent to the use of your personal information as set out in this Privacy Statement. We may use your personal information together with other information for the purposes of processing your bets, making decisions about and managing your account, administering the services we provide and researching information for our demographic profiles.

 **10Bet** is the sole owner of the personal information we collect from our clients; we do not share it with any third party. We will not give, trade or sell this information to any organization or business, or to any individual not employed by us.

If a client provides personal information while in contact with our customer service departments, we will use it only for the purpose of customer service. We will not sell a client’s phone number to telemarketers or anyone else.You are entitled to a copy of the information we have about you. If any of the information you have provided us with changes at any time or appears to be incorrect or you wish to receive a copy, please contact us.

 ** _Use of Cookies  
_**  
We may use cookies as a means of collecting information from a web server for the above purposes following a customer's use of the website. We do not monitor the activities of individual customers.  
 **  
10Bet** does not disclose to advertisers any information about individual customers.
